Operation Blood Hunt is a action, adventure, horror
film directed by Louis Mandylor.
Prolific expert of the occult and whiskey, Reverend Conte, accompanies a ragtag group of military rejects to a remote South Pacific Island to
investigate the disappearance of Marines units  stationed there in 1944, said to be at the hands of the Japanese Imperial Army.
Upon speaking  with the island’s inhabitants, they soon discover the Marines had actually
been massacred by a group of Lycanthropes, known to most as WEREWOLVES.
The Reverend, played by Quinton 'Rampage' Jackson.
Murphy, played by Jonathan Rhys Meyers.
Richter, played by Louis Mandylor.
Heirani, played by Sonia Couling.
Billy the Kid, played by Myles Clohessy.
BlackJack, played by Gary Cairns.
Operation Blood Hunt is a 2024 Thai-American war action horror film
written by Brandon Slagle and directed by  Louis Mandylor.
It stars Quinton Jackson, Louis Mandylor,
Jonathan Rhys Meyers and Sonia Couling.
The film is about a group of military that investigate the disappearance of the
marine units who assigned to the remote part of South Pacific Island.
The film explores themes of world war ii, south
pacific, amused, japanese imperialism.
The tone is dark.